Morning.
Good morning.
I'm preparing breakfast for everyone.
Making rice noodle rolls.
I know you said yesterday.
I also know where your sauce is.
Is this rice noodle roll sauce?
No.
Isn't this it?
The sauce needs to be...
The sauce needs to be cooked and simmered.
Really?
I'm not sure if I can make it successfully.
Because I haven't made it for a very long time.
Don't have too high expectations.
It's okay.
Even if you don't succeed, Ke Yu will still eat it.
You watch him eat.
Where is Ke Yu? Why isn't he awake yet?
What's going on?
Morning.
You need to chop this up.
Why don't you wash this first?
Okay, I'll wash it.
It should take a while.
Go wash it over there.
You're dressed so hip today.
With a dog in the middle.
Very beautiful.
I'll put it plainly.
Give it to me.
It's okay.
There are not many left.
No.
I think you're too slow.
Look.
You cut it too finely.
I want it finely chopped.
Too finely chopped.
It's for rice noodle roll.
It's not in chunks.
It's minced.
I'll do it.
It needs to be minced.
It looks good.
Let me chop it again.
Ke Yu.
Here's another knife.
Okay.
Double blade, okay?
Double blade.
Is it enough?
Yes, absolutely.
Okay.
I'm going to
Make the sauce for you.
This is the secret recipe for Bao Bao's rice noodle roll sauce.
I researched it online,
And then combined it with my own taste,
And then I made it.
This is incredibly fragrant.
Add water.
Stir it up.
It's starting to take shape.
It smells good, right?
Here you go.
Bao, do you want to eat it?
Is this bun tasty?
Then I'll eat it.
Is it okay?
It's so delicious.
You stand here.
On his shoulder, right.
Three, two, one.
So cute.
Quite good at taking photos.
Let me try it.
My rice noodle roll.
Extremely delicious.
Really?
Very tasty, really very tasty.
A thousand miles of marital connection, a single thread ties.
A ribbon ties the two of you together.
Yesterday, teaming up relied on goodwill.
Whether in sync or not depends on ability.
For the details, please check the bulletin board.
I'm full.
Guys, I'll go read the bulletin board for you.
Today is an outing day.
We will start the journey of popular partner protection.
Three pairs of partners
Will be tied together with ribbons throughout the journey.
Ribbon?
Tie our hands with ribbons?
As the popular partners, Bao Bao and Ke Yu
Will accept the challenges initiated by the other two pairs of partners,
And cannot refuse.
The winning pair of each challenge
Can shorten the ribbon of the losing pair by 20 centimeters.
The pair with the most wins in the end
Will receive the Most Compatible Partners honor.
Now, please put on the ribbons.
Now, right now.
We want to challenge Ke Yu and Bao Bao.
That means we can initiate a challenge randomly now.
We can initiate a challenge in our hut.
We can also initiate a challenge outside.
What to challenge?
Let's find something in the room to challenge first.
How about we play that gaming console, that Dazzling Dance?
Let's go.
I agree, let's play games.
Okay.
Let's just say,
We'll easily beat you.
Too 'arrogant', I can't stand it.
It's time to test the understanding.
Dynamic Duo Dance.
How long has it been since you danced?
Seriously dancing, it's been
Over a year.
I danced a while ago.
Whoever initiates the challenge dances first.
You dance first.
She initiated the challenge first.
Right.
You go.
Sit.
Right.
Come on.
They are so cute.
I think we are going to mutate.
I'm going to mutate.
That's it.
Two stars.
This group has fallen apart.
Come on, next challenger.
Come on.
It's up to you, buddies.
We can win.
Pull up my pant legs a bit.
The Gemini is here.
Do you know what dance is?
I'll tell you later.
Is that it?
That's it.
Okay.
Feels good.
Dancing very similarly.
All Dance Kings.
They are in sync.
It's going to be over.
It's going to be on my face.
Yingbo.
No way. They are going to get five stars.
I think we got a high score.
They must have got over 9,000.
It's very high.
Oh, no.
Come on.
I'm not confident.
Me neither.
Let's dance this one.
No, don't.
Let's just dance this one.
Why do I have to dance a girl group dance?
Bro.
What? You can't?
I'll dance for you.
Wait, let me find it.
This one, this one is good.
Let's go.
It's time to test your understanding.
Why is it like this?
Why did you choose such a difficult one?
Too difficult.
Sure to win.
Quick.
Still can score.
Wave your hand.
Look.
Just let it sense that you are moving.
How do you turn this?
We have a good chance.
Let me tell you.
Look at the one below.
Then look for that arm in the direction of your arm.
Up, down, down, to the right, down.
Then this way, then up, then down.
To put it plainly.
All perfect.
I can't see anything but perfection.
We're more in sync.
You're really good at dancing, Bao Bao.
And it's very joyful to dance.
Can we achieve 5,000?
10,000.
Almost there.
We're the best in the entire game.
What are you cheering for?
♪Frankly, what can be done about such difficulty♪
Each team shrinks by 20 centimeters.
Okay, that's fine.
For fairness,
I accept.
I'm convinced.
20.
That's how long.
You also shrink by 20, hurry up.
We shrink.
What do you say, guys?
What do you say?
Shall we change the game?
Like riding a bike.
Let's see who can ride up there in one go.
Don't waste the bicycles here, right?
Wait, I need to use the bathroom.
I need to change clothes later.
How about we find a sports hall
To play basketball or roller skate?
Let's go roller skating.
Sure.
Let's go, set off.
Let's go.
Go.
Come here.
Let's just put this line here.
Don't let anyone pass.
Don't let them pass.
What do you mean?
Only those with long legs can pass.
We're off.
I think the three groups should come up with group names today.
Each group comes up with one.
I think our group should be called
Burning Summer.
No retreat.
Is it that long?
The latter part is in brackets.
Why do you call it Burning Summer?
Because I think we are the most exciting.
Exciting.
Is there something on my face?
Here.
If we win the game,
We have no retreat.
And you guys...
No.
What are you taking?
Don't peek.
How did AI come into this?
Really funny.
The veteran artist can't rub it, right?
Quick, the veteran artist, rub it.
We are called 'Whatever We Do Is Right'.
Is it okay? It's just that simple.
Whatever we do, we do right.
Okay.
What about your slogan?
Then let's just say this.
I never lose.
We never...
We want to say it in Cantonese.
I...
Never...
Do...
Don't say it like that.
Just listen to me.
I.
Never.
Will.
Not.
Lose.
I never lose.
No.
Teach me in Cantonese.
I never lose.
I don't want to hear it.
Really.
Let him read it.
It's the same.
We've decided.
That's it.
How about it?
Okay.
Let's use the most imposing voice
To introduce our team's
Name and slogan.
We are
Set Sail and Chase Dreams.
We are Burning Summer.
Absolutely
No retreat.
We are called Whatever We Do Is Right.
Our slogan is...
Source text.
Let's see today.
Let's compete.
No problem.
They can slide backward.
This is so amazing.
They're sliding hand in hand.
How do you do this?
Do you know how to do it?
I don't know.
Put it on.
Then lift it up and it will tighten.
And then do the same on this side, go left.
Thank you for the reminder.
Wait a moment.
I want to try it.
Let me try.
Go.
Is it okay?
Why can't I slide?
Relax.
Is it okay?
Okay.
You need to speed up to rush over.
Directly stabilize it.
Then go over.
Slow down.
I have to edge first.
I'll lead you.
Wait a moment.
Why don't you go ahead?
You can't skate at all.
Do you need us to teach you?
No need.
Do you need me to teach you?
Okay.
Don't teach me.
Let's go.
Wait a moment.
Let me turn around.
You are so tall.
Just slide forward.
I'll let you hold my hand.
Wait a moment.
Relax.
Don't move.
Try sliding on it.
No way.
If I don't move,
It will keep expanding outward.
It expands outward and moves inward.
Expand outward and move inward.
What does "expand outward" mean?
What does "move inward" mean?
It means to expand outward,
And then move inward.
Expand outward, then move inward.
Be a bit more free.
You can
Change direction.
Like a couple.
Two people walking there with the wall.
Like they are living their lives.
Just like this, step by step.
As long as you glide a bit longer,
You'll know that feeling.
Look, they can all skate now.
Wait a moment.
Source text.
Do you know?
We are now on the waves.
Let's go.
Sit for a while.
Bao Bao.
Why are you so scared?
Bro,
Do you know what he looks like?
Did you see him?
I saw him.
That's just how he is.
Sit for a while.
He's afraid of too many things.
I'm already used to it.
Sit.
You go get a "Anti-slip Mat".
Get an "Anti-slip Mat"?
Yes, come.
I'll get you an "Anti-slip Mat".
We want one too.
Okay.
I'll bring it.
Do you feel safe now?
It seems a bit safer.
Then go ahead and slide as you please.
Okay.
Don't laugh.
I won't laugh.
Come on, let's go.
We'll slowly get used to it ourselves.
Just like this.
Take it slow.
Hold my hand like this.
Hold this one of mine.
Wait a moment.
How do I...
Your hands are sweating.
I am...
I'm really scared.
I'm right here.
Take it slow.
Just like this.
Very good.
One step at a time.
Right?
Right.
Don't be afraid.
Fear is the biggest obstacle.
As long as you're not afraid of it,
You won't be afraid of falling,
Or whatever.
You won't feel there's a problem.
But when I'm about to fall, you must let go.
Got it?
Otherwise, I'll pull you down.
Look, you're already sliding.
Do you feel it?
You're already on the right track.
To put it plainly, right.
To put it plainly, you're on the right track.
Really on the right track.
That's how it is.
You've already got it.
Awesome.
Sit for a while.
Too tired.
Let's go over and find them.
This is mainly a 'fart kill'.
What are we competing in?
How do you say?
Compete in what?
Come on.
We set off at the same time.
Whoever is the slowest wins.
Okay.
Start right here.
Is that okay?
Okay.
We don't care about winning or losing.
Let's go.
Follow me, Bao.
Now I am the elder sister.
You are the younger brother.
Okay.
Then call me sister.
Sister.
Buddies.
Start from this slope.
To that pillar.
Which pillar?
That pillar.
That glowing pillar.
Go.
She's pushing me.
Ke Chun.
He's messing with me.
Mess with him.
You can't go back.
We have to mess with them.
We can't go back.
Then we'll be cannon fodder.
Then let you win.
Let you win.
See?
We won again.
This is just cheating.
Frankly speaking,
Let me tell you,
The game is more fun when you cheat.
They don't move.
You must get moving.
Come over and push them.
Push them over first.
Let's pretend to fight each other
To lure Ke Yu and the others over.
You're sliding back too.
No.
We'll fight in a bit.
You bad thing.
Push them.
I can't wait
To see what happens
When you fall into my hands.
What are you doing?
Mess with them.
No.
Don't push her.
Alright.
Go.
No, we will never concede.
No.
We are the winners.
Then we lost, okay?
We lost.
Okay.
Let me sit for a while.
Let's have a race.
Ke Yu, do you dare to challenge?
Come on.
Is this okay?
We set a particularly short distance.
One side restrains the other side to slide blindfolded
To the finish line.
Bro, why don't you let me slide on one foot?
You can slide slowly.
I'll hold you while you slide.
Slide blindfolded. One person slides blindfolded,
And another person guides.
It can be like this, so it's fair for everyone.
Right.
Okay.
Come on.
I'll go get the blindfold.
Then you just stand straight, right?
I'm blindfolded, right?
Right, I think it's the same for you.
You hold onto my waist.
Let's practice walking first.
Look.
You can also try it.
Sure.
You hold me.
I'll do the sliding.
Okay.
Give it a try now.
Let's go.
You hold me.
I'm holding you.
Right, just hold onto my shoulder.
Hold onto my shoulder.
I don't even need to hold you.
I can just push you.
Super stable.
Once we get there, just sit and watch him.
Okay, let's turn back.
From this yellow line to that yellow line.
Is that okay?
Oh my.
They're so fast.
That's too scary.
Blindfold.
They're quite fast.
They're really fast.
Because she's light.
It's okay to lose.
It doesn't matter.
Are you ready?
Yes, come on.
Three.
Two.
One.
Slow down.
You're too fast. Wait a moment.
Hold my hand.
Be careful. We need to brake at the end.
We lost.
It's okay. We lost.
Really? So fast?
They were too fast.
Because they
Started quickly.
Really?
Okay.
We almost lost.
Really.
They might be just this close to us.
You guys are so fast.
How was it?
Okay.
Do you want to race again?
No.
Actually, it doesn't matter whether we cut it short or not.
Cut it however you like.
Because the two of us are already at zero distance.
We are all skating experts here.
We can look over here.
The game of Red Light, Green Light will start in the arena.
Red Light, Green Light.
How about we challenge this one?
Okay.
We can play the game.
Those who want to participate
Can come to our starting line.
Stand in front of the starting line.
When I say the keyword, "red light",
You must do the corresponding action.
Listen to my command.
3, 2, 1, freeze in a hug.
Return to the starting point.
Go back.
3, 2, 1, interlock fingers, freeze.
Interlock fingers.
Don't move.
This pose is okay.
Everyone was moving just now.
Everyone, return to our starting point.
Source text.
Wait, wait a moment.
My foot.
What's wrong?
I can't do this anymore.
It hurts?
Right.
Did you sprain your ankle?
Did you sprain it?
No, it's just too tight.
It's too tight for my feet.
These shoes are too tight.
Bao Bao, do you want to come?
I can't fight alone.
It's okay, I'll play barefoot with you.
I'll play barefoot with you.
Barefoot.
Play barefoot.
It should be fine for you to wear your own shoes, right?
Okay.
I'll bring your shoes over for you.
But you can't slow down Bao Bao's sliding speed.
You can't hold her back.
You must run forward with her when she's sliding.
I will.
Come on.
Good players, get ready.
Listen to the command again.
Three, two, one.
Heart gesture, freeze.
This time it's quite standard.
Listen to the command again.
Three, two, one.
Pat head, freeze.
Okay, listen to my command again.
3, 2, 1, princess carry, freeze.
We won.
Fortunately, I didn't wear those ice skates.
How could I have managed a princess carry?
Look at Zhao Yingbo.
Alright, players, get ready.
Listen to the command again.
I touched...
Our game of freeze tag is over.
So much fun.
I just love playing this kind of game.
Although I lost, I was quite happy.
Right.
Wait, look at them, that's fun.
Ke Yu,
You can definitely play this.
Do you want to give it a try?
Come on.
Why don't you
Put your hand on Bao Bao's shoulder,
Or my shoulder.
It's okay.
I'll put my hand on her shoulder.
Go.
Start.
The little train starts.
Wait a moment.
Hold on tight to me.
Isn't it too fast, buddy?
Don't be afraid.
Don't be afraid. We won't fall.
Wait a moment. Be careful.
Slow down.
A bit slower.
Don't pull my flesh.
I'm not pulling your flesh.
He's going to fall.
Isn't it fun?
Fun.
Train head.
Not so wonderful.
I feel like he's going to fall.
Okay.
That's about it.
Let's change places.
Okay, we'll continue to challenge you.
Bring it on.
The next destination is the basketball court.
Let me tell you what
2.45 meters of air is like.
What do we do now?
Go away.
Steal his ball.
You can't have long nails for basketball.
It hurts so much.
What should we do? We're still competing.
Step on me.
I step on him.
Sit on my shoulders.
I'm so tall.
We have always been the strongest.